megawebpromotion.com 2012-09-20

# Website Promotion * Free Traffic * Free URL Submission * Free Website Traffic

At MegaWebPromotion.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. By using our website and purchasing services from us, you agree to be bound by this policy. Should we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page to keep you informed of what information we collect and how we use it. 

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**   
When you visit our website, MegaWebPromotion.com collects your IP address which is used to administer our website and improve the quality of our services. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information that does not personally identify you. 

To order services from us you must provide “billing information” such as your name, billing address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number or checking account number. This information is necessary for us to process your order, to notify you of your order status, and occasionally notify you about changes to our website, new services, or special offers you may find useful. 

**How We Protect Your Information**   
Our website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use secure servers when you place an order on our website. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts all information you send to us. All customer data is similarly protected against unauthorized access. 

We will not share your information with third parties unless you have consented to the disclosure or the disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or legal process, protect or defend our rights or property, protect our customers from misuse or unauthorized use of the MegaWebPromotion.com website, protect the personal safety or property of our customers or the public, or to fulfill customer orders. 

MegaWebPromotion.com may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, customers, sales, and related website information to third parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

When MegaWebPromotion.com submits your URL, classified ad, or other listing to third party websites we submit the information that you have provided and are not responsible for any of the actions of those parties, the content of their websites, their privacy standards and policies, or any services they may offer. 

**Cookies**   
The MegaWebPromotion.com website uses “cookies”, which are small pieces of information that are stored on your computers hard drive. These cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, and allow us to store your information between visits. Cookies may also be used by our affiliates or advertisers. MegaWebPromotion.com encourages anyone who uses cookies to follow appropriate privacy standards and policies, but is not responsible for cookies placed by third parties. 

**Your Feedback**   
MegaWebPromotion.com welcomes your questions and comments regarding our privacy policy. Please email us at 

This Privacy Policy last updated July 01, 2004. 

|   |
